tagcrowd.com 2017-08-22

# TagCrowd: Privacy

## Your Privacy

TagCrowd is committed to protecting your privacy. We don't have user accounts and don't require registration, so you are free to visit and use our site anonymously.

Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. See also our Terms of Service.

### What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When you use TagCrowd.com to create a word cloud, we don't store any information you submit. It exists on our server for the milliseconds it takes to process and generate a word cloud, then is immediately deleted.

The only time we ever collect identifying information is when you purchase a license for commercial use or donate to TagCrowd. This is done through PayPal, which protects the security of your financial information. We only receive your Name and Email Address through this transaction. This allows us to keep track of who has purchased a license and who has donated.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other party for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.

### How does TagCrowd protect customer information?

We use PayPal's secure server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the internet and sent to us. We never receive any financial information because PayPal protects your financial privacy. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

### What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.

### Will TagCrowd disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

TagCrowd does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. TagCrowd may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

TagCrowd may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://tagcrowd.com/tos.html>

### In Summary

TagCrowd is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

### Your Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TagCrowd.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Questions and Feedback

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at [contact@tagcrowd.com](mailto:contact@tagcrowd.com)
